(Howard:)It's amazing people keep coming
to comic book stores...
...instead ofjust downloading
comics digitally.
(Leonard:)It's probably for the best.
(Leonard:)For a lot of these guys,
the weekly trip here...
(Leonard:)...is the only chance their mom has to go
to the basement and change their sheets.
(Howard:)Oh, that reminds me,
I get fresh sheets tonight. Yay.
Well, what do you think
of new comic book night?
(Sheldon:)Magic, huh?
(Amy:)Sheldon, I'm disappointed.
(Amy:)As a brilliant man,
you're entitled to a vice.
(Amy:)I could understand frequenting
an opium den...
(Amy:)...or hunting your fellow man
for sport.
(Amy:)But this? Lame-o.
(Sheldon:)A, comic books employ storytelling
through sequential art...
(Sheldon:)...a medium that dates back 17,000 years
to the cave paintings of Lascaux...
(Sheldon:)...and B, you play the harp,
Iike that's cool.
(Stuart:)Can I help you find anything?